Once you have found a signal that seems to indicate the future performance of a stock,
找到似乎能表示股票未来业绩的信号后
it is time to put it to action.
就该采取行动了
For instance, if you think that a stock has upward momentum,
例如 如果你认为股票具有上升动量
you might want to buy some shares and hold onto it for a fixed period of time,
你可能想要买入一些股票并持有一段时间
or until you start seeing the stock fall.
或者买入后持有 直到股价下跌时才卖出
This is known as taking a long position on the stock.
称之为做多股票
When you sell your stock, hopefully,
当你希望以高于买入价格
at a higher price than you bought it,
卖出股票时
that is known as closing your position.
称之为平仓
But what if the stock has a downward momentum?
但如果股票具有下跌动量呢？
And you believe that it is going to keep falling for some time?
并且你认为它将继续下跌一段时间
In this case, you can take what is known as a short position on the stock,
在这种情形下 你可以做空股票
selling first and then buying back later,
先卖出 之后买入股票
hopefully, at a lower price.
你会希望买入价格更低
If this is the first time you're hearing about shorting,
如果你第一次听说卖空股票
it might sound bewildering.
可能听起来有点令人困惑
But what it boils down to is borrowing shares from someone,
实际上就是从他人那借入股票
usually your broker, and then promising to
通常向经纪人借入
return them once your short position is closed.
并且承诺在空头被平仓后 还给他们
The brokers incentive here is that they typically
经纪人这么做的动机是
earn a commission on the profit you make from the short sale.
在你从卖空交易中获利后 通常他们也能从中赚取佣金
At the same time, they are taking a risk.
与此同时 他们也会承担风险
What if you bail out and never buy back the shares?
如果你退出了 并再也没有买回这些股票 可怎么办
For this reason, brokers typically require you to keep some money in
所以 经纪人通常要求你在保证金帐户中保留一定的金额
a margin account that they can charge if you fail to keep your promise.
如果你没能兑现承诺 他们能够从这个帐户中扣款
The whole process of short selling is a bit more complex with interests,
整个卖空流程比较复杂
fees, and margin calls coming into the picture.
需要考虑利息 费用和追加保证金
But, all you need to know when evaluating
你只需记住
a potential trading signal is that shorting is one possible action you can take.
在评估潜在交易信号时 卖空是一种可以采取的行动
So, when you think a stock is going up,
当你认为股价将上升时
you can buy or go long,
你可以买入或做多
and if you believe it is going to keep falling, you can short it.
如果你认为股价将下跌 你可以做空
However, dealing with individual stocks can be tricky and unpredictable.
但是 实际股票处理起来比较麻烦并且难预测
You don't want to put all your eggs in one basket.
你不能将所有鸡蛋都放在一个篮子里 孤注一掷
Therefore, it is recommended to adopt a cross-sectional strategy,
建议采取横截面策略
where you invest in multiple stocks at the same time.
即同时投资多支股票
One smart way to do this is to use your signal to rank order the stocks,
一种做法是利用信号对股票排名
and use the rankings to select stocks for long and or short positions.
并根据排名选择多头和空头股票
For instance, if you're using a momentum signal,
例如 如果你采用动量信号
the top performers are likely to keep rising,
表现靠前的股票很有可能继续上涨
so you can go long on them,
所以可以做多它们
and the bottom performers,
底部的股票在下跌
that are falling, are likely to keep falling.
并且很有可能继续下跌
So, you can short them.
所以可以做空它们
This has the added benefit that you're using
这么做还有一个优势
the relative performance of stocks to compare them.
即你利用了股票的相对业绩来比较它们